ACTWU's General Executive Board (GEB) Records 5619/030
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU's General Executive Board (GEB) Records
1916-1988
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. General Exectutive Board
Textile Workers' Union of America. General Exectutive Board
5619/030
9 cubic feet
9 linear feet
Correspondence, reports, publications.
This collection consists of minutes, reports, and correspondence of the General Executive Boards of Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union. Also included are the minutes of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America Committee of Nine.
6826518
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
May 10, 2010
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, July 2010
Biographical / Historical
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors' and cutters' locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW's craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership's advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards' by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union-owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor's involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman's participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor's Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman's prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union's political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union's existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related collections: 5619: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America 5619/003: ACWA's Sidney Hillman Scrapbooks 5619/004: ACTWU's Jacob Sheinkman Records from the Sectretary-Treasurer's and President's Offices. 5619/004 mf: ACTWU's Microfiche Collection of Jacob Sheinkman's Speeches 5619/006: ACTWU's Executive Vice-President's Office Records 5619/010: ACWA's Jacob Potofsky Records from the President's Office 5619/018: ACTWU's Secretary-Treasurer's Office Records 5619/029: ACTWU's Vice-President's Office Records 5619/036: ACTWU's Murray Finley Records from the President's Office 5619/036 mf: ACTWU's Microfilm of Murray Finley's Correspondence from the President's Office And all other 5619 collections.
Textile industry--New York (State)--New York; Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State)--New York; Clothing trade--New York (State)--New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. General Executive Board--Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; Textile Workers Union of America; Textile Workers Union of America. General Executive Board--Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
6826518
- Volume I: General Executive Board Minutes, Nov. 10-11, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Hotel Carlton, Washington D.C.
- Volume I: General Executive Board Minutes, August 11, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Volume I: General Executive Board Minutes, June 9 and June 16, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  General Office
- Volume I: General Executive Board Minutes, April 16-18, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Atlantic City, NJ
- Volume I: General Executive Board Minutes, Dec. 9-10, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Volume I: General Executive Board Minutes, May 16-17, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Wardman Park Hotel, Washington D.C.
- Volume I: General Executive Board Minutes, Sept. 19-20, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Hotel Sinton, Cincinnati, OH
- Volume I: General Executive Board Minutes, Nov. 6-7, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Hotel Willard, Washington D.C.
- Volume I: General Executive Board Minutes, June 5, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Volume I: General Executive Board Minutes, August 30-31, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  General Office and Hotel New Yorker
- Volume I: General Executive Board Minutes, May 8-10, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Hotel Royal York, Toronto
- Volume I: General Executive Board Minutes, May 6-8, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Mount Royal Hotel, Montreal
- Volume I: General Executive Board Minutes, August 8-9, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Morrison Hotel, Chicago
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, Dec. 10, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, Nov. 4, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Boston, MA
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 12, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  President Hillman's Office
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes,August 6, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, Sept. 17, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  President Hillman's Office, Committee of Nine
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, May 2, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Hotel Brevoort, NYC, Committee of Nine
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, April 16-17, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Ritz Carlton Hotel, Atlantic City, NJ
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, Jan. 14, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  National Office
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, Dec. 4-6, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Chicago, IL
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 3-4, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, July 7-8, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, May 1-3, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, Feb. 28, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, Nov. 28, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Chicago, GEB Finance Committee
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, Nov. 14-16, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, August 2, 5-6, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, July 24, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  General Office, Finance Committee
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, June 20-21, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, Dec. 2, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 9-11 and Nov. 1, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  San Francisco, CA
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, August 18-21, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, August 9-11, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  Hotel New Yorker, NYC
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 13-17, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, August 23, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, May 4-6, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Volume II: General Executive Board Minutes, March 11-12, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, May 3-8, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  Hotel Ambassador East, Chicago, IL
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, November 1, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  Hotel Warwick, Philadelphia, PA
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, December 2, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, January 20th, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  Approved Resolution
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, March 20-21, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  Hotel Commodore, NYC
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, May 8-13, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  Ambassador Hotel, Chicago, IL
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, August 14, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 12, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, Nov. 18, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  Hotel Stevens, Chicago, IL
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, January 12, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, March 13, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Ground Lease, Springler van Beuren Estates, Inc. to Union Square Realty Corp., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- General Executive Board, CIO Political Action Committee, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- General Executive Board, Canadian Congress of Labor, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- General Executive Board, Norwegian Federation of Labor, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, July 19-20, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, Nov. 22-24, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  Hotel Mayflower, Atlantic City, NJ
- General Executive Board, Loan to UAW, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, April 29-May 3, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, July 13, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, August 22, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, Nov. 15, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- General Executive Board, Contribution to Sidney Hillman Foundation and Pocketbook Workers' Union, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  Approved Resolutions
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, Feb. 5-7, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- General Executive Board, Contribution to National Federation of Telephone Workers, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, May 9, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  Commodore Hotel, NYC
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, August 6-8, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  Hotel Sheraton, Rochester, NY
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 12, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 23, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, Dec. 11, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- General Executive Board, Contributions, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, Feb. 3, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- General Executive Board, Contribution to United Packinghouse Workers, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, May 3, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, May 20, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  McAplin Hotel, NYC
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, August 24, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- General Executive Board, Contribution to Oil Workers International Union, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Volume III: General Executive Board Minutes, January 27-29, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  Washington, D.C.
- General Executive Board, Resolutions to All Joint Boards, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Volume IV: General Executive Board Minutes, May 8, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  Cleveland, OH
- General Executive Board, Loan to Oil Workers International Union, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Volume IV: General Executive Board Minutes, Sept 15, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  Asbury Park, NJ
- Volume IV: General Executive Board Minutes, March 28-30, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Volume IV: General Executive Board Minutes, May 24-25, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Volume IV: General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 8, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Volume IV: General Executive Board Minutes, Jan. 23, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Volume IV: General Executive Board Minutes, May 5, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  Traymore Hotel, Atlantic City, NJ
- Volume IV: General Executive Board Minutes, June 10, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  New York
- Volume IV: General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 31, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 88)
- General Executive Board, Contribution to the FDR Foundation, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Volume IV: General Executive Board Minutes, Dec. 8-9, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Volume IV: General Executive Board Minutes, July 28, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  Lake Placid, NY
- General Executive Board, Referendum Elections, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 92)
- Volume IV: General Executive Board Minutes, Sept. 23, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 93)
- Volume IV: General Executive Board Minutes, Jan. 29, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  Amalgamated Bank, NY
- Volume IV: General Executive Board Minutes, June 11, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Volume IV: General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 7-9, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  Statler Hotel, St. Louis, MO
- General Executive Board, Local #1712 Charter, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 97)
- General Executive Board, Charter of Amalgamated Life Insurance Co., Inc., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 98)
- General Executive Board, Agreement and Declaration of Trust for the Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 99)
- General Executive Board, Agreement and Declaration of Trust for the Amalgamated Cleaners & Dyers Insurance Fund, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 100)
- General Executive Board, Agreement and Declaration of Trust for the Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Insurance Fund, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 101)
- General Executive Board, Agreement and Declaration of Trust for the Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Retirement Fund, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 102)
- General Executive Board, Agreement and Declaration of Trust for the Amalgamated Journeymen Tailors Retirement Fund, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 103)
- General Executive Board, Agreement and Declaration of Trust for the Amalgamated Laundry Workers Insurance Fund, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 104)
- General Executive Board, Agreement and Declaration of Trust for the Amalgamated Neckwear Workers Insurance Fund, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 105)
- General Executive Board, Agreement and Declaration of Trust for the Amalgamated Neckwear Workers Retirement Fund, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 106)
- General Executive Board, Agreement and Declaration of Trust for the Amalgamated Retail Retirement Fund, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 107)
- General Executive Board, Agreement and Declaration of Trust for the Amalgamated Retail Insurance Fund, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 108)
- General Executive Board, Agreement and Declaration of Trust for the Amalgamated Washable Clothing, Sportswear and Allied Industries Insurance Fund, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 109)
- General Executive Board, Agreement and Declaration of Trust for the Amalgamated Washable Clothing, Sportswear and Allied Industries Retirement Fund, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 110)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, March 31, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 111)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, May 4, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 112)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, Sept. 22, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 113)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, Feb. 22, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  Shoreham Hotel, Washington D.C.
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, Feb. 22, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 115)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, July 11, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  Marcy Hotel, Lake Placid, NY
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 20, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 117)
- General Executive Board, Contribution to the American Institute of Men's and Boys' Wear, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 118)
- General Executive Board, Contribution to flood victims in the Northeastern US, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 119)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, Dec. 3, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 120)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, Jan. 24-26, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 121)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, May 15-23, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 122)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, August 13, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 123)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, Jan 21, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  Resolutions
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, April 25, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 125)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, May 13, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 126)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, Nov. 13, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 127)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, Feb 12, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 128)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, May 5-16, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 129)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, July 7, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  Magnolia, MA
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, Nov. 10, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 131)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, March 24-26, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 132)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, July 6-10, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  Montreal, Canada
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, Sept. 17, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 134)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, Dec. 14-17, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 135)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, March 3-7, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 136)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, July 21-23, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 137)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, August 28, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  Special Meeting
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, Nov. 17-19, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 139)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, Feb. 26 - March 4, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 140)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, March 18-29, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 141)
- General Executive Board, All Joint Boards and Local Unions and the 1970 Referendum Election (Box 1, Folder 142)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, Nov. 10-12, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 143)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, Dec. 2, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 144)
  Warwick Hotel, NYC
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, Feb. 25 - March 4, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 145)
- Volume V: General Executive Board Minutes, March 3 & 24, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 146)
  Approved Resolution and Minutes
- General Executive Board Minutes, Aug. 16-19, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 147)
  Mark Hopkins Hotel, San Francisco, CA
- General Executive Board Minutes, Nov. 19-20, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 148)
  Americana Hotel, Miami Beach, FL
- General Executive Board, Charges against Hartner & Resolution on Gladys Dickason, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 149)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Reports, Goals on Feb. 23-26, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 150)
  Miami Beach, FL
- General Executive Board Minutes, May 22 - June 1, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 151)
- General Executive Board, Hartner Law Suit, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 152)
- General Executive Board Minutes, August 9, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 153)
  Madison hotel, Washington D.C.
- General Executive Board Minutes, Special Meeting on August 30, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 154)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Special Meeting on Sept. 6, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 155)
  General Office, NYC
- General Executive Board Minutes, Special Meeting on Sept. 13, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 156)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Special Meeting on Sept. 16, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 157)
  New York Hilton Hotel, NYC
- General Executive Board Minutes, Nov. 9, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  New York Hilton, NYC
- General Executive Board, Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board Minutes, March 5-8, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Farah Plant, Miami Beach, FL
- General Executive Board Minutes, June 4-7, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Toronto, Ontario
- General Executive Board Minutes, Oct. 24-25, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- General Executive Board Minutes, Jan. 28-31, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  San Diego, CA
- General Executive Board Minutes, Sept. 16, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  NYC
- General Executive Board, Charges against Diana Nunes, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Local #177